Come get the new election song for the
first day of polling, set to the most
cue-2
fashionable tune, written in a humorous
style, guaranteed to raise a
cue-3
smile. Yes, after an age of campaigning,
the election's begun. When it will
cue-4
end, nobody knows. It could go on for
days, weeks even, or get stopped early if
cue-5
the great decide. So as people vote, I've
been hired to make sure these old interest
cue-6
songs get passed around the polling
place, and sung too. And they're going
cue-7
like hot cakes. They're making a laughing
stock of that new interest candidate, Sir
cue-8
Neddy Turner. No bad thing either. He's
changed his mind and his political
cue-9
principles so many times, the name Turner
fits him like a glove. It's just like the
cue-10
-song says.
-In Oxford fair county some folks make a
cue-11
rout. But let us consider what is there
about. Why all is concerning the choosing
cue-12
a night, who has oft turned his coat but
never turned right.
cue-13
Da-da-n-da-dee-n-da-dee-n-da-da.